lipperhey.com 2019-10-02

# Lipperhey Respects your right to Privacy

## Privacy of your information

At Lipperhey, we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our clients. We understand that as a customer, the privacy and security of confidential information are important.  
The purpose of our Privacy Policy is to outline our practice in this area.

* * *

## Security of Information

Lipperhey is located in the Netherlands. Any information that you provide to Lipperhey will be transferred to the Netherlands. By providing personal information to us, you are therefore consenting to its storage and use as outlined. Lipperhey will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, unauthorized alteration, destruction or other malfeasance.

When you place an order with us online, we collect information about you, including your name, address and credit card information. This information is necessary in order for us to process and complete your order. Product registration information includes acquiring your serial number as well as your name.

Lipperhey has always reserved the right to limit free technical support to registered users. The only way to assure that you will be entitled to free technical support for a product in the future is to register with Lipperhey. Product upgrade, pricing and special offers are only available to registered users.

## Collection of Personal Information

Lipperhey collects general usage information from our website's visitors. This is done with the help of cookies. Cookies are small files which a website transmits to your hard drive when you visit that site. Cookies cannot read information from your hard drive nor can it read information from other cookies if the setting has been disabled. However, you will still be able to access and browse the Lipperhey website even if the cookies have been disabled. 

## Use of Personal Information

Lipperhey may use personal information that has been collected to:

  * Provide you with news of new information that may be of interest to you.
  * Determine your eligibility to receive support at our discretion.
  * Survey you (and others) in an attempt to improve our website, products, or business.
  * Improve the quality of our website.
  * Help us analyze general traffic patterns throughout our site.
